Finding Aid for the Collection of Research Materials Related to Linguistic-Psychological Studies of Genie (pseudonym), 1895-2003, 1970-2003 LSC.0800
UCLA Library Special Collections
- 4. Guardianship, 1970-1978
  - 4D. Miscellaneous, 1971-1978
    - Care instructions for Genie while the Rigler's are away, ca. 1972 (Box 54, Folder 38)
    - David Rigler's notes on Genie's situation, 1978 January 16 (Box 54, Folder 39)
    - Material related to foster situation with Greenan and Kodamo, 1978 March (Box 54, Folder 40)
      Includes notes from David Rigler.
    - Material related to Jean Butler., 1971 August 26; undated (Box 54, Folder 41)
    - Placement in Beatrice Mansfield family home, 1975 November 7 (Box 54, Folder 42)
      Paperwork from California Health and Welfare Agency.
    - Report of facility evaluation, 1974 June 21 (Box 54, Folder 43)
      Report of unannounced site visit of the Rigler's home.
    - Rigler's application for child care license, 1971 August 15 (Box 54, Folder 44)
    - Social worker's post-visit summary report, 1973 October 25 (Box 54, Folder 45)
      Prepared by Constance K. Young
    - Tablet with David Rigler's handwritten notes, 1971 September 30-1971 December 13 (Box 55, Folder 1)
      Notes on the decision to foster Susan Wiley and meeting notes regarding Jean Butler.
    - Termination of Genie's social security benefits, 1973 February 3 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Text for Genie explaining her history, ca. 1971 (Box 55, Folder 3)
      Possibly written by Marilyn Rigler.
    - Various Material, 1971 December-1978 September (Box 84, Folder 22)
    - Various Material, 1971 December-1978 September (Box 55, Folder 4)
      Includes paperwork regarding Genie's education and health and the Rigler's foster care paperwork.
    - Various material regarding Jean Butler, 1971 September 18; 1972 December 4 (Box 84, Folder 23)
    - Various material regarding Jean Butler, 1971 March 7-December 11 (Box 55, Folder 5)
      Correspondence and reports regarding Genie's temporary placement.
- 5. Lawsuit, 1978-1984
  Series includes correspondence, miscellaneous notes, and a variety of legal paperwork including complaints, summonses, depositions, interrogatories, and the final settlement agreement for case number C 276459. Some of these materials, due to privacy concerns, may be inaccessible to researchers. Please consult the Manuscripts Librarian in advance so that access arrangements can be made as appropriate.
  - Requests for information by Jean Butler from Childrens Hospital of Los Angeles, 1978 January 23 and 27 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence--Freedom of Information Act request for grant no. R12 MH21191, 1978 February 28 (Box 55, Folder 7)
    Response by Department of Health, Education, and Welfare to FOIA request of Jean Butler with note to David Rigler.
  - Correspondence--Rigler, David, 1978 April 27 (Box 55, Folder 8)
    Unopened and returned letter originally sent to Genie.
  - Case number C 276459, 1979 March 14-1984 February 13 (Box 55, Folder 9)
    Summons, Second amended complaint, Substitution of attorney, settlement agreement
  - Correspondence--Childrens Hospital of Los Angeles memorandums, 1979 April 9-1981 September 9 (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence--Carlisle, C.J. to David Rigler, 1979 May 8 (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Interview with David Rigler by Farmers Insurance Group regarding Wiley lawsuit, 1979 May 18 (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Interview with David Rigler by Farmers Insurance re: Lawsuit (Box 84, Folder 24)
    This file is open for research. Duplication is strictly prohibited
  - Correspondence--Home & Clifford to David Rigler, 1980 April 7; 1980 December 15 (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - Various correspondence regarding Genie's medical and research records, 1980 May 16-1980 June 17 (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence--Rigler, David to Susan Grant, 1980 June 11 (Box 55, Folder 15)
    Regarding need to preserve records.
  - Case number C 276459--Deposition of Howard Hansen, 1981 January 23 (Box 84, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence--Rushfeldt, Shelley & McCurdy to David Rigler and Howard Hansen, 1981 March 12-November 18 (Box 84, Folder 26)
    File is open for research. Duplication is strictly prohibited.
  - Correspondence--Rigler, David to Randall L. Shelley of Rushfeldt, Shelley & McCurdy, 1981 July 9 (Box 84, Folder 27)
  - Case number C 276459--Responses to interrogatories by David Rigler, 1981 November (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence--Shelley, Randall L. to David Rigler, 1981 October 20 (Box 55, Folder 20)
    Includes attachment regarding interrogatories.
  - List of possible witnesses, ca. 1981 (Box 55, Folder 21)
    Written by David Rigler.
  - Correspondence--Skuse, David to David Rigler, 1982 December (Box 55, Folder 22)
    With Dr. Rigler's response.
  - Case number C 276459--Various materials, 1983 September 12-1984 September 19 (Box 55, Folder 23)
    Notice of taking deposition; Copy of request for dismissal; correspondence.
  - Case number C 276459--Deposition of Howard Hansen, 1983 November 2 (Box 84, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence--Rushfeldt, Shelley & McCurdy to David Rigler, 1983 November 17-1984 February 13 (Box 55, Folder 25)
  - Case number C 276459--Deposition of David Rigler, vol. 1, 1983 December 16 (Box 55, Folder 26)
  - Case number C 276459--Deposition of David Rigler, vol. 2, 1983 December 17 (Box 55, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence--Rigler, David to Kenneth Drake of Rushfeldt, Shelley & McCurdy, 1983 December 28 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    Lists potential defense witnesses and discusses Jean Butler.
  - Questions to ask Jean Butler with notes by David Rigler, ca. 1983 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Yellow letter tablet with handwritten notes by David Rigler, ca. 1983 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence--Rigler, David to Rushfeldt, Shelley & McCurdy, 1984 January 17 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Case number C 276459--Settlement agreement and correspondence, 1984 April 24; 1984 May 10 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Case number C 276459--Settlement agreement and correspondence (Box 84, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence--Rigler, David to Irene Wiley, Howard Hansen, and Susan Curtiss, 1984 June, September (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence--Rigler, David to Irene Wiley, Howard Hansen, and Susan Curtiss (Box 84, Folder 30)
    This file is open for research. Duplication strictly prohibited.
  - Correspondence--Shelley, Randall L., 1984 August 24 (Box 56, Folder 7)
    Letter copied to David Rigler and Howard Hansen regarding Wiley v. Childrens Hospital of Los Angeles
  - Correspondence--Shelley, Randall L. (Box 84, Folder 31)
  - 6. Miscellaneous, 1968-2003
    Series consists of article clippings, correspondence, material related to Genie's medical history and care, printed material, notes, ephemera, and other assorted items. Some of these materials, particularly the medical files, may be inaccessible to researchers due to privacy concerns. Please consult the Manuscripts Librarian in advance so that access arrangements can be made as appropriate.
    Arranged in subseries A-D as follows:
    6A. Clippings
    6B. Correspondence
    6C. Medical files
    6D. Assorted notes and papers.
    - 6A. Clippings, 1970-1994
      Various articles about Genie and related cases and issues.
      - Assorted on Genie's discovery, 1970 December 5; 1979 March 18; undated (Box 84, Folder 33)
        This folder is open for research.
      - Shryock, Harold / Sleeping intellects: why you should be glad your child is curious / Harold Shryock, 1971 April (Box 84, Folder 34)
        Mentions Genie's case.
        This file is open for research.
      - Computers simulate physiological systems, 1971 June 7 (Box 84, Folder 35)
        From C&EN.
      - Linguist studies development of girl isolated for 11 years. Interview with Victoria Fromkin, 1972 October 25 (Box 84, Folder 36)
        From Eugene, Oregon Register-Guard, page 2E.
      - Girl's Sleep Eyed, 1975 July 22 (Box 84, Folder 37)
      - Profs hope to bring ape-boy to Boston, 1976 May 14 (Box 84, Folder 38)
        San Francisco Examiner, pg. 16.
      - Retarded girl used for profit, suit alleges, 1979 March 18 (Box 84, Folder 39)
        Los Angeles Times, Part I: 22.
        This file open for research.
      - Pines, Maya / Civilizing of Genie, 1981 September (Box 84, Folder 40)
        Psychology Today, pg. 28-34.
      - Cutting through the silence. Review of Russ Rymer's book, 1993 May 2 (Box 84, Folder 41)
      - A 'wild child' conflict: science vs. compassion, 1994 October 17 (Box 84, Folder 42)
        Review of NOVA documentary.
      - Spitting into the wind, ca. 1977 (Box 84, Folder 43)
        Clipping from British newspaper on the fostering of a disturbed 12-year old girl. No publication data.
      - Compendium of photocopied stories on Genie's discovery, 1970 November 16-1970 December 16 (Box 79, Folder 1)
      - Genie - The 'Wild Child' of California, 1981 October 4 (Box 79, Folder 2)
        From San Francisco Chronicle.
      - Various articles on Genie, 1992 June-1993 June 13 (Box 79, Folder 3)
        Includes Natalie Angier's review of Rymer book from New York Times Book Review and David Rigler's response.
      - Various articles on Genie's discovery and family, 1970 November 17-1970 December 16 (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - 6B. Correspondence, 1970-2003
      Subseries includes correspondence from Russ Rymer, author of articles and a book about Genie, miscellaneous correspondence from public interested in Genie's case, various letters regarding documentary productions, and other assorted items.
      - Requests for information on Genie's case, 1970 December 24-1971 July 6 (Box 56, Folder 22)
        From students at various schools.
      - Cards and letters sent to Genie by the general public, 1970 December-1971 April (Box 56, Folder 23)
      - Price, Donna, 1971 March 16 (Box 56, Folder 24)
        To Genie from young girl who read of her story.
      - Copy of inter-departmental memo to Howard Hansen regarding Mrs. Wiley, 1971 July 23 (Box 56, Folder 25)
      - Various correspondence., 1971 August-1974 November 11 (Box 56, Folder 26)
      - Requests for information on Genie, 1972 July 5-1975 October 21 (Box 56, Folder 27)
        General requests from the public.
      - Fromkin, Victoria to David Rigler, 1972 December 8 (Box 56, Folder 28)
      - Secher, Allen and Richard Milton to David Rigler, 1974 April 11 (Box 56, Folder 29)
        Regarding documentary film project.
      - Various correspondence regarding visit of Peter Griffiths from Royal Hospital for Sick Children in Glasglow, Scotland, 1975 April-July (Box 56, Folder 30)
      - Kagan, Jerome to David Rigler, 1975 May 29 (Box 56, Folder 31)
      - Hanzik, Marjorie to Marilyn Rigler, 1975 August 11 (Box 56, Folder 32)
      - Hoffman, Kay to David Rigler, 1975 October 17 (Box 56, Folder 33)
        Regarding production of Genie's story.
      - Fromkin, Victoria to David Rigler, 1976 February 11 (Box 56, Folder 34)
      - McGrath, Marian, 1978 November 9 (Box 56, Folder 35)
        To David Rigler regarding payment for paper publication. Dr. Rigler's draft reply is also included.
      - Lucas, Martin, 1981 January 8 (Box 56, Folder 36)
        To David Rigler regarding possible British documentary on Genie.
      - Rymer, Russ to David Rigler, 1988 September 22-1993 June 30 (Box 56, Folder 37)
      - Rymer, Russ to David Rigler, 1988 September 22-1993 June 30 (Box 84, Folder 44)
      - Reactions of Rigler friends and associates to Rymer's New Yorker article, 1992 April 18-1993 June 26 (Box 56, Folder 38)
      - Garmon, Linda, 1992 May 6-1994 December 20 (Box 56, Folder 39)
        Various correspondence from producer for NOVA documentary on Genie.
      - Miner, John to David Rigler regarding Russ Rymer's article, 1992 June 2 (Box 56, Folder 40)
        Includes photocopy of letter Miner sent to Russ Rymer.
      - Rigler, David to Linda Garmon, WGBH - NOVA producer, 1992 July 17, November 14, December 24 (Box 56, Folder 41)
      - Rigler, David to Russ Rymer, 1992 July 19, August 5; 1993 July 8 (Box 56, Folder 42)
      - Wiley, Irene to David Rigler, 1992 August 21-1993 July 20 (Box 56, Folder 43)
      - Rigler, David to Irene Wiley, 1992 September 5-1993 January 30 (Box 56, Folder 44)
      - Sage, DeWitt to David Rigler, 1992 October 8 (Box 56, Folder 45)
      - Rymer, Russ--various material, 1992 October 12-1993 April 30 (Box 56, Folder 46)
      - Rigler, David to Gail Eisen, 1993 January 23 (Box 56, Folder 47)
      - Schaub, Ben to David Rigler, 1993 April 7; 1993 June 22 (Box 56, Folder 48)
      - Rigler, David to Rebecca Sinkler, 1993 May 30 (Box 56, Folder 49)
      - Reader reactions to New York Times Book Review article, 1993 June 10 and June 13 (Box 56, Folder 50)
      - [Mabel ?], 1994 November 4 (Box 56, Folder 51)
        Personal note to David and Marilyn Rigler regarding NOVA documentary.
      - Wiley, Irene. Photocopy of letter to the Riglers, 1996 June 15 (Box 56, Folder 52)
      - Viewer's reaction to NOVA special, 1996 September 13 (Box 56, Folder 53)
      - NBC Dateline, 1997 February 8-25 (Box 56, Folder 54)
        Letters and email from Michael Mierendorf and Evelyn Maturana to David Rigler.
      - Feldman, Gina, 1997 April 15 (Box 56, Folder 55)
        Fax to David Rigler regarding planned documentary by NHK.
      - Tokyo Broadcasting System to David Rigler, 2003 September 19 (Box 56, Folder 56)
    - 6C. Medical files, 1970-1977
      Subseries consists of material regarding Genie's medical care and history. Included are dental x-rays, charts, hospital records, nursing care plans and notes, immunization information, dental records, Medi-cal paperwork, results from various tests, and assorted notes and material.
      - Genie's height and weight record, 1970-1974 (Box 57, Folder 1)
      - Notes from nurses and doctors from original hospital stay, 1970 November 4-1971 January 21 (Box 57, Folder 2)
        Includes a rough draft of a pre-admission case history and spiral notebooks.
      - Hospital records of [Genie] from Childrens Hospital of Los Angeles (1 of 2), 1970 November 4-1971 August 11 (Box 57, Folder 3)
        Medical history, progress notes, order sheets, medication and treatment sheets, and patient activity sheets.
      - Hospital records of [Genie] from Childrens Hospital of Los Angeles (2 of 2), 1970 November 4-1971 August 11 (Box 57, Folder 4)
        Bedside records, temperature charts, and nurses notes.
      - Occupational therapy evaluation and initial notes, 1970 November 12-1973 June 28 (Box 57, Folder 5)
      - Nursing care plans, 1970 November 20 and 24 (Box 57, Folder 6)
      - Genie's dental x-rays, 1971 January 27 (Box 57, Folder 7)
      - Patient records from Childrens Hospital of Los Angeles for Genie, 1971; 1975; 1977 (Box 57, Folder 8)
      - Genie's enuresis report, 1972 March 18-1972 April 5 (Box 57, Folder 9)
      - Immunization certificate for Genie, 1972 May-September (Box 57, Folder 10)
      - Genie's enuresis chart, ca. 1972 (Box 57, Folder 11)
      - Genie's enuresis chart, ca. 1972 November (Box 57, Folder 12)
        Some of the notations are in Genie's handwriting.
      - History and testing of Genie's hearing, 1974 June 18-1975 April 17 (Box 57, Folder 13)
      - Notes and documentation on Genie's hearing problem, ca. 1975 (Box 57, Folder 14)
      - Medi-Cal patient identification card, 1975 (Box 57, Folder 15)
      - Miscellaneous medical paperwork, 1975 March 16 (Box 57, Folder 16)
      - Miscellaneous letter from Genie's dentist, 1975 June 25 (Box 57, Folder 17)
      - Paperwork from Eastern Los Angeles Regional Center for the Developmentally Disabled regarding medical testing for Genie, 1975 October 15-16 (Box 57, Folder 18)
      - Merci School and Activity Center student medical evaluation, 1976 June 17 (Box 57, Folder 19)
      - Medi-Cal paperwork. Includes photograph, 1977 January 28 and March 30 (Box 57, Folder 20)
        Includes photograph of Genie.
      - Medical request for stay in hospital for Genie, 1977 April 29 (Box 57, Folder 21)
      - Progress notes regarding psychiatric session [author unknown], 1977 May 3 (Box 57, Folder 22)
      - Genie's enuresis chart, 1972 (Box 80, Folder 9)
    - 6D Assorted notes and papers, 1968-1993
      Subseries consists of a variety of miscellaneous items including printed material, notes, ephemera, and other assorted pieces.
      - Printed Material--Southwest Regional Laboratory for Educational Research and Development / Word attack skills: review of literature, 1968 June (Box 57, Folder 23)
      - Printed Material--Schechter, Marshall D., et al / Perceptual isolation therapy: a new experimental approach in the treatment of children using infantile autistic defenses, 1969 January (Box 57, Folder 24)
        Reprinted from Journal of the American Academy of Child Psychiatry, Volume VIII, No. 1
      - Printed Material--Protection of the individual as a research subject, 1969 May 1 (Box 57, Folder 25)
        Printed by U.S. Department of Health, Education, and Welfare.
      - Personal identification of Father, ca. 1970 (Box 58, Folder 1)
      - Personal identification of Father, ca. 1970 (Box 84, Folder 45)
        This file open for research. Duplication strictly prohibited.
      - Pencil sketches of Genie in rehabilitation, 1970 November (Box 58, Folder 2)
        Artist unknown.
      - Various material received by Dr. David Rigler from Dr. James Kent, 1970 November 4-1971 September 18 (Box 58, Folder 3)
        Brief history of Genie, correspondence, notes, etc., received by Dr. Rigler in 1979.
      - Various material received by Dr. David Rigler from Dr. James Kent, 1970 November 4- 1971 September 18 (Box 84, Folder 46)
      - Rigler, Marilyn--Pacific Oaks College placement service application, 1971 May 16 (Box 58, Folder 4)
        Includes Marilyn Rigler's resume and educational history.
      - Butler, Jean--Receipts for rubella tests, 1971 June 25 and 1971 July 6 (Box 58, Folder 5)
      - Small reading primer presented to David Rigler by Jean Butler, ca. 1971 July (Box 58, Folder 6)
        Includes two brief handwritten notes.
      - Printed Material--Committee on linguistics, Stanford University / Papers and reports on child language development/No. 3, 1971 December (Box 58, Folder 7)
        Compendium of five documents.
      - Rigler, David--Curriculum vitae, ca. 1972 (Box 58, Folder 8)
      - Printed Material--Program on voice disorders in school children: clinical management, 1972 May (Box 58, Folder 9)
        Compendium of articles from program sponsored by California Department of Education, April 26-28, and, May 8- 10, 1972 in San Francisco and Los Angeles.
      - Printed Material--Research related to children bulletin 31, 1972 September-1973 February (Box 58, Folder 10)
        A bibliography of articles and studies.
      - Rigler, David--Notes, ca. 1973 (Box 58, Folder 11)
      - Rigler, David--Yellow notepad with various notations, ca. 1973 (Box 58, Folder 12)
      - Rigler, David--Notes, 1973 April 28 (Box 58, Folder 13)
        Stenographer's notebook.
      - Rigler, Marilyn--Master's thesis "The case of Genie", 1974 (Box 58, Folder 14)
      - Rigler, Marilyn--Master's thesis "The case of Genie", 1974 (Box 84, Folder 47)
        File open for research. Duplication strictly prohibited.
      - Printed Material--Rogers, Linda / Cerebral dominance [BIS Conference Report no. 34], 1974 February (Box 58, Folder 15)
      - Publisher's release, 1975 February 24 (Box 58, Folder 16)
        To publish "The Linguistic Development of Genie" in book.
      - Rigler, David--Notes, 1974 April 3-May 15 (Box 58, Folder 17)
      - Printed Material--UCLA Educator/Volume 17, no. 2, 1975 Spring (Box 58, Folder 18)
        Contains articles by Stephen D. Krashen and Joseph E. Bogen.
      - Brown, Roger / [Book chapter excerpt], 1976 July 16; 1976 August 1 (Box 58, Folder 19)
        Includes manuscript originally sent to David Rigler for comment. Also includes correspondence which discusses the chapter.
      - Ephemera--Flyer for Susan Curtiss's book "Genie: A psycholinguistic study of a modern-day 'wild child'", ca. 1977 September (Box 58, Folder 20)
      - Rigler, David--Notes, ca. 1978 (Box 58, Folder 21)
      - Rigler, David--Notes regarding telephone conversation with Irene Wiley, 1993 February 13 (Box 58, Folder 22)
      - Rigler, David--Response to Natalie Angier's review, 1993 April-June (Box 58, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence--Butler, Jean to David Rigler, 1984 October 10; 1984 October 23 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence--Wiley, Irene to David Rigler, 1984 October 15 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence--Wiley, Irene to David Rigler (Box 84, Folder 32)
  - Hand written notes by unidentified author, ca. 1984 (Box 56, Folder 10)
- 7. Photographs, ca. 1895-1993 (bulk 1970-1977)
  Included in the series are color slides, color prints, black and white prints, negative film, and contact sheets.
  - Various images of Irene Wiley's family., 1895-ca.1920 (Box 59, Folder 1)
    Some photos taken in Eugene, Oregon.
  - Various images of Irene Wiley's family., ca. 1920-1960 (Box 59, Folder 2)
    Scanned images that had been mounted in a photo album. Sheets have been removed from album.
  - Genie at approximately 2 years old with brother, ca. 1960 (Box 59, Folder 3)
    Negatives made from film received from Genie's mother.
  - Irene Wiley's family including grandmother and son Johnny, 1970 December (Box 59, Folder 4)
    Color prints.
  - [Wiley home?], ca. 1971 (Box 59, Folder 5)
    8x10 b/w prints made from color transparencies sent by Dr. Jay Shurley.
  - Various pictures of Genie, ca. 1971-1975 (Box 59, Folder 6)
    Color and b/w prints.
  - Various montages of Genie with descriptive captions, 1971-1975 (Box 59, Folder 7)
    Includes photos of tantrum behavior and Larry Solow teaching Genie sign language.
  - Images of Genie's drawings, 1971-1976 (Box 59, Folder 8)
    Color slides.
  - Language acquisition charts, 1971 June-1974 November (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Genie in outdoors environments, 1971 August-September; 1972 November (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Genie on carousel and at park, 1971 September (Box 59, Folder 11)
    3 x 5 color prints. From envelope labeled no. 3.
  - Wooden blocks on carpeted floor, 1971 September (Box 59, Folder 12)
    3 x 5 color prints.
  - Genie on carousel and playing with big ball, 1971 September-November (Box 59, Folder 13)
    Negative film. From envelope labeled no. 93.
  - Genie in tub and playing with model, 1971 October (Box 59, Folder 14)
    3 x 5 b/w prints. From envelope labeled no. 91.
  - Genie playing beside fountain playing with water, ca. 1972 (Box 59, Folder 15)
    5 x 7 color prints.
  - Genie sitting on floor with unidentified woman and looking at doll in carriage, ca. 1972 (Box 59, Folder 16)
  - Genie, with head down, sitting in a chair, ca. 1972 (Box 59, Folder 17)
    Negative film. Other miscellaneous images on the film.
  - Genie's room [?] with objects, ca. 1972 (Box 59, Folder 18)
    3 x 5 color prints. From envelope labeled no. 85.
  - Miscellaneous photographs, ca. 1972 (Box 59, Folder 19)
    Color print and b/w print.
  - Two images of Genie smiling, ca. 1972 (Box 59, Folder 20)
    Color and b/w print.
  - Various images of Genie, ca. 1972 (Box 59, Folder 21)
  - Various images of Genie grooming, playing, exploring, and interacting with others, ca. 1972 (Box 59, Folder 22)
    B/w contact sheets. Negative film.
  - Various images of Genie, some with Marilyn Rigler, 1972 (Box 59, Folder 23)
    Color and b/w prints. From envelope labeled no. 6.
  - Behaviors and toilet training charts, 1972-1973 (Box 59, Folder 24)
  - Genie, the Arcadia home, and objects, 1972-1975 (Box 59, Folder 25)
    5 x 7 color prints. Appear to be copies of slide images.